KEMAL TAUFIK FIKRI (MR.) TELECOMMUNICATION ENGINEERING STUDENT

Mobile: +62 89692785818 Cicukang 03/09 Arcamanik 40294 kemaltaufikf@gmail.com Bandung, Indonesia

https://www.linkedin.com/in/kemal-taufik-

fikri-6885621a2/

PROFILE

I am a student of Bandung State Polytechnic. I'm really interested to elevate social and humanitarian fields in Indonesia. I have volunteered in community service activities and participated to do some researches in technology field with my other comrades.

EDUCATION

Politeknik Negeri Bandung, Indonesia

2018-Present

Currently pursuing Bachelor's Degree at Bandung State Polytechnic majoring in Telecommunication Engineering with radio frequency and network engineer expertise as specializations.

HONORS AND AWARDS

Pass the Vocational Student Entrepreneurship Program

2021

Successfully passed the independent business proposal selection in the PWM program (Vocational Student Entrepreneurial Program) and received a fund of IDR 17,000,000 by the *Direktorat Pendidikan Tinggi Vokasi dan Profesi*.

Pass the Vocational Student Entrepreneurship Program

2021

Successfully passed the selection of independent business proposals in the KBMP program (*Kompetisi Bisnis Mahasiswa Polban*) and received a fund of IDR 7,500,000 by the DIPA Politeknik Negeri Bandung.

CCNA: Switching, Routing, and Wireless Essential – Cisco Academy

2020

National Creative Ideas and Design 2019

2019

The 1st Runner Up of National Creative Ideas and Design 2019 held by the Ministry of Research, Technology and Higher Education State Polytechnic of Malang.

National Poster Creative Ideas

2019

The Champion of National Poster Creative Ideas and Design 2019 held by the Ministry of Research, Technology and Higher Education State Polytechnic of Malang.

The speaker of "Be Religious and Smart Generation"

2019

The speaker of "Be Religious and Smart Generation" event held by the Student Executive Board of UPI Law Civics Student Association, on december 8th - 9th 2018.

Pekan Kreativitas Mahasiswa Karsa Cipta Belmawa

2021

A participant of PKM KC Direktorat Kemahasiswaan Direktorat Jenderal Pembelajaran dan Kemahasiswaan Kementrian Pendidikan dan Kebudayaan 2021 with title Intelligent Parking System Based on Face Recognition and License Plate Recognition as a Parking Land Security Solution.

Pekan Kreativitas Mahasiswa Karsa Cipta Belmawa

2020

Passed the funding proposal of PKM KC 2020 Directorate of Student Affairs, Directorate General of Learning and Student Affairs, Ministry of Education and Culture with the title of Smart Watches for Drowsiness Detection of Motor Vehicle Drivers by Utilizing Heart Rate Variability.

Pekan Kreativitas Mahasiswa Karsa Cipta POLBAN

2020

Passed the funding proposal of PKM KC 2020 Politeknik Negeri Bandung with title Facial Recognition and Number Plate Recognition Based Smart Parking System.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Life Plan Journal

2020-Present

Founder

- Currently in charge of project Planner 2022 (Present)
- Manage to make the official website of the life plan journal (Jan 2021)
- Being one of the four presenters on IG Live at a self development event entitled "Plan the Future, Together with the Life Plan Journal" (Jul 2021)
- Successfully produced and sold 1000 dotted notebooks (Jan 2021)
- Created and sold 1000 self development books (November 2020)
- Held job vacancies in all provinces of Java Island (>60 resellers, agen, and dropshipper spread in big cities in Java Island) (November 2020)

Ma'had Al-Mujaddid

2019-Present

Head of IT department

- Head of the IT division in charge of the student database website creation project (Present)
- Successfully searched for aid funds at kitabisa.com/mahadalmujaddid for IDR $3,594,215 - (Jul\ 2021)$
- Successfully made the logo of the Ma'had Al-Mujaddid mosque (June 2021)
- As a director in the videography project, 35 Ramadan lecture videos on YouTube (2018-2020)

ORGANIZATIONAL ACTIVITY

DF2

2020-Present

- Created and managed skill building program
- Lead alumni's Of DKM Daarul fikri event

Telecommunication Students Association *Member*

2018-2020

- Led the HIMATEL's Ramadhan hospitality events
- As a performer of the 2020 prayer together

KKN 2019-2020

Event Committee

• Volunteer in Cukul Village development events (theme: Stepping Up to the Higher Level of Insightful People)

• Volunteering in Nanggerang Village Development Events (theme : Building Synergy for Our Nation)

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Frontend developer : CSS (Beginner), HTML (Beginner), Javascript

(Beginner), Bootstrap (Beginner)

Backend developer : MySQL (Beginner), PHP (Beginner), Pyhton (Beginner),

Network engineering : Cisco Packet Tracer (Beginner)

IoT : Arduino (Intermediate), Raspberry Pi (Beginner), Proteus

(Intermediate), Jetson Nano (Beginner)

Other programming language: VBA Code (Intermediate), Java (Beginner), Matlab

(Intermediate), Assembly (Intermediate)

Graphic design: Photoshop (Advance), Illustrator (Intermediate),

Dimension (Beginner), Adobe Animation (Intermediate).

Video & Audio editing : Premier Pro (Advance), After Effect (Beginner), Adobe

audition (Intermediate), Audacity (Intermediate), FL Studio

(Beginner).